[Music] let's
[Música]
see what's happening with Twitch, okay if you're in the
a ver lo de Twitch vale si estás en los
skit you have to team up with gibel
skit tienes que hacer Team con gibel
to support each other because
para apoyarse todo mutuamente porque
everyone, let's see what's happening with
todo el mundo a ver lo que pasa con
Twitch. It's been a month or so,
Twitch Es que hace un mes y pico
doing a debate with Ricky, one of the
haciendo un debate con Ricky uno de los
debates we did on space, eh,
debates que hicimos por space eh se me
some photos came up on my screen, they are the
coló en pantalla unas fotos que son las
famous Easy photos, not these from
famosas fotos de Easy no estas del
patreon, in which, to my taste,
patreon en las que para mi gusto no se
nothing bannable looks, to my taste,
ve nada baneable para mi gusto no se ve
nothing bannable looks if you're telling
nada baneable si tú me estás diciendo a
me that there's hyper explicit content.
mí que hay un contenido hiper explícito
Okay, well, okay, but
Vale pues Vale pero es que no se veía
nothing bannable looked okay. But still, in the middle of a
nada baneable okay Pero igualmente en
live stream, they banned me for
pleno directo me banearon por contenido
explicit content. So, I'm saying, well, I'll accept the
explícito Total que digo Bueno asumo el
7-day ban and when I come back, well, that
ban de 7 días y cuando vuelva pues ya
's not my main problem, no, Twitch.
estar no es mi principal problema Twitch
Besides, it's an extra income, what I
no Además es un ingreso extra lo que yo
make on Twitch a month is very small, I
hago en Twitch al mes vale muy pequeño o
mean, I don't know if I earn 300 or 400 euros some
sea no sé si cobro 300 400 eur algunos
months, okay, from Twitch. But, well, they come in
meses vale de Twitch Pero bueno vienen
handy, they come in handy, but, well, if they've
bien vienen bien pero bueno si me han
banned me, then I say, well, I'll wait  7 days
baneado pues digo Bueno me espero 7 días
What happens is that on the second day or
Lo que pasa es que al segundo día o por
so while I'm banned I get another ban I
ahí estando baneado me llega otro Ban me
get a ban for evading the suspension
llega un baneo por evadir la suspensión
and from what I was looking at evading the
y por lo que estuve mirando evadir la
suspension is that you are doing
suspensión es que que tú estés haciendo
things to evade the suspension and for
cosas para evadir la suspensión e por
example that I go to another live stream from
ejemplo que yo vaya a otro directo de
another Twitch streamer or that I create
otro streamer de Twitch o que me cree
another account like what happened to megamax no
otra cuenta como le pasó a megamax no
So what I thought
Entonces qué es lo que yo me pensaba que
was because of the gibel issue no because
era por el tema de gibel no porque
gibel was live also no
estaba gibel en directo también no
While they banned me then
Mientras que me banearon entonces pues
inevitably well I appeared there not
inevitablemente pues aparecí por allí no
where gibel and where cel Ricky couldn't
donde gibel y donde cel Ricky no pudo
report Ricky was live p
reportar Ricky estaba en directo p
creating with me his followers most
creándose conmigo sus seguidores muy
likely okay they were the ones who
probablemente vale fueron los que
reported I mean if the followers
reportaron o sea si los seguidores
were the ones who reported surely of course
fueron los que reportaron seguramente
that is more than obvious because if I had
claro eso es más que evidente porque si
n't finished the live I delete
no hubiera terminado el directo Yo borro
and that's it I delete the live like I always
y punto borro el el directo como siempre
do and that's it okay eh Total that I did
hago y punto vale eh Total que que
n't give it much importance
tampoco que le diera mucha importancia
I sent the appeal they rejected it for my
mandé la apelación me la rechazaron por
[ __ ] face that's what you are
la [__] cara es lo que me estás
rejecting me here from the appeal if not I have
rechazando aquí de la apelación si yo no
not made any  Ban evasion and
no he hecho ninguna evasión de del Ban y
what they've told me is that there was an
lo que me han dicho es que había una
account out there called jabi
cuenta por ahí que se llamaba jabi
oliveira 2 that was broadcasting on
oliveira 2 que se ponía a emitir en
Twitch, my content from here we saw it the
Twitch mi contenido de aquí lo vimos el
other day no So I understand that it must have
otro día no Entonces yo entiendo que
been for one thing or another I
habrá sido o por una cosa o por la otra
say Well then I wait the
digo Bueno pues ya está yo me espero los
six months that you have to wait to
se meses que hay que esperarse para
try again to peel and and circle sneaks
intentar otra vez pelar y y cir cuela
such and such what I didn't count on was that we
tal y cual lo que yo no contaba era con
weren't going to be banned anymore in
que no íbamos a estar vetados ya en Los
Squid Games okay eh the other day when I
juegos del calamar vale eh el otro día
saw that Ricky came in well
cuando cuando vi que entraba Ricky pues
I say [ __ ] but well maybe he makes
digo [__] pero bueno a lo mejor hace
some contact I don't know what but I've already
algún contacto no sé qué pero ya me he
found out that we're not banned I've already found out
enterado que no estamos vetados ya me he
that we're not banned by
enterado que no estamos vetados por twi
rival twi because the team is not the same
rival porque el equipo no es el mismo
also Okay what's going on well that
además Vale qué es lo que pasa pues que
I'm banned and being banned well I
estoy baneado y estando baneado pues no
can't be in Squid Games it's not
puedo estar en los hos del calamar no
for me eh family is not for me
está para mí eh familia no está para mí
so today no no Of course in the elan and
entonces hoy no no Claro en los elan y
things like that I can't be in anything no no
esas cosas yo no puedo estar en nada no
I can't be in  nothing where there are
no yo no puedo estar en nada donde haya
people broadcasting on Twitch I can't
gente que esté emitiendo en Twitch yo no
be no you can't create another
puedo estar no no puedes crear otro
channel I mean there's an Absurd rule on
canal O sea hay una norma Absurda en
Twitch which is that if you are banned you can't
Twitch que es que si tú estás baneado no
appear on another channel they ban
puedes aparecer en otro canal banean a
the other person or rather imagine what a
la otra persona o sea fíjate tú qué
stupid and unfair way because on top of that you
manera tan tonta e injusta porque es que
send them the appeal and they
además le le mandas la apelación y se lo
explain it to them And they haven't even read it because
explica Y es que ni la han leído porque
I haven't done any
es que yo no he hecho ninguna evasión de
B evasion let's say I haven't done any B evasion nor was the
B vamos ni he hecho evasión de B ni el
content for which I was banned
contenido por el que me banearon era
explicit the 7 day ban doesn't happen either the
explícito el ban de los 7 días tampoco
7 day ban I say Well
lo pasa que el de los 7 días digo Bueno
come on I have no choice but oh well
venga va no me queda otra pero bueno
family That's the situation okay
familia Esa es la situación vale yo
when I found out these days that we
cuando me he enterado en estos días de
weren't banned the gossip channels
que no estábamos vetados los canales de
in the series okay Well
salseo en la serie vale Eh pues lo que
what I've contacted the
lo que me he puesto en contacto con las
two or three people that I think
dos o tres personas que yo creo que
may have I'm not going to say names okay
pueden tener no voy a decir nombres vale
but the two or three people with
pero las dos o tres personas que con las
whom I have more or less good vibes
que tengo más o menos buen rollo
cordiality and that I think may
cordialidad y que yo creo que pueden
have power or contact Okay and  They're
tener poder poderío o contacto Vale y
trying to talk about it there okay No
están intentando ahí hablarlo vale No no
we can't guarantee anything because you already know
podemos garantizar nada porque ya sabéis
that TT nobody is banned okay let's see I do
que TT no está nadie vetado vale a ver
n't have much hope honestly But
no tengo mucha esperanza la verdad Pero
well I'm trying say well to
bueno yo lo intento dig bueno por
ask what's left no And if
preguntar lo que no quede no Y si de
suddenly between now and Monday they took away the
repente de aquí al lunes me quitasen el
B they managed to get them to take away the B
B consiguieran que me quitasen el B
then the second then the second
luego los segundo luego los segundo
would be that they give me a space that I have
sería que me den un hueco que me quede
a space left Because if they already have all the
un hueco Porque si ya tienen todos los
guests the hair you understand me and I'm
invitados la pelo me entiendes y me temo
very afraid that yes that everything is going to be
mucho a que sí a que va a estar todo
taken they will take it away from you One day later they will take it away they will
ocupado ya te lo quitarán Un día después
take it away when I'm already
me lo quitarán me lo quitarán cuando ya
no let's see they will take it away from me It's that it's that
esté no a ver me lo quitarán Es que es
already Even if they take it away today or tomorrow
que ya Aunque me lo quiten hoy o mañana
or the day after it might be there's no space no no they won't
o pasado lo mismo ya no hay hueco no no
lift the ban surely
me quitarán el baneo seguramente
when is it is it's that I didn't expect that
cuando es que es que yo no me esperaba
the date was going to be now I mean I
que la fecha iba a ser ahora o sea yo me
thought that this was going to be the
creía que esto iba a ser los juegos del
squid games which is the only thing like that in which I
calamar que es lo único así en lo que yo
more or less want to participate
más o menos me hace quiero participar
you know well we had a great time and
sabes pues nos lo pasamos muy bien e y
I expected that it would be like
yo me esperaba que sería como por
March April or around there you know And then that's why
marzo abril o por ahí sabes Y entonces
like I wasn't in a hurry or
por eso como que no me corría prisa o no
I wasn't worried too much about Twitch, really,
me preocupaba mucho lo de twit la verdad
but well, that's the circumstance. If
pero bueno esa es la circunstancia si
Auron came back with Gemita, you'll also come back with
auron regreso con gemita tú también con
Twitch. Cheer up, Red Heart King. I don't think so,
Twitch ánimo Rey corazón rojo No creo
okay. But well, I've asked for it, I've
vale Pero bueno yo lo he pedido lo he
asked around, I've told
preguntado por ahí le he dicho a
Comanche that I'm trying to
Comanche que estoy intentando
solve it, and then the issue is that there's
solucionarlo y y el tema luego es que
space. Very good, my beloved public,
haya hueco muy buenas mi amado público
how are you? We have a controversy, let's go with the squid
qué tal tenemos polémica vamos con los
game, Comanche is coming
jueguecito del calamar que Comanche
back. I didn't want to get into the
vuelve no quería meterme en polémicas de
squit controversy, but yesterday Aon and r already talked.
los squits pero ayer Aon y r ya hablaron
After
Después de
several conversations with Twitch, so to
varias conversaciones con Twitch Por así
speak, I feel forced. H. I thought that
decirlo me veo obligado H Yo pensaba que
this one had said no to any
este había dicho que no a cualquier tema
organizational issue so as not to harm his
organizativo para no perjudica a sus
colleagues. If I'm honest with you with the
compañeros Si le soy sincero con la
new attitude that I want to form, the new
nueva actitud que quiero formar la nueva
stage that I'm forming, I don't know what I'm
etapa que estoy formando no s si que
going to do, I'm going to try to get it
vaya a hacer yo yo voy a intentar
out. But tell Comanche to talk
sacarlo Pero dale a Comanche que hable
to Twitch, let's see, eh, of course,
con los de Twitch a ver eh claro es que
we're asking a lot. It's not asking them to
estamos pidiendo mucho no es pedirle que
invite me, it's asking them to invite me and
me inviten es pedirle que me inviten y
asking them to talk to Twitch so that they can
pedirle que que hablen con Twitch para
unban eh of course it's asking too
que me quiten el baneo eh claro es pedir
much I mean I don't have that much of a relationship with
mucho o sea no tengo tanta relación con
anyone for that let's go Likewise to
nadie como para tal vamos Igualmente a
the two people that I think are
las dos personas que yo creo que que son
more powerful or may have more more
más poderosas o puedan tener má más
contact or more power not on Twitch than those
contacto o más poder no en Twitch de las
I have access to I have
que a las que yo tenga acceso se lo he
told them I have commented and and they are They
dicho se lo he comentado y y están Están
are consulting if those two people
están consultando si esas dos personas
can't neither of the two m but let's
no no pueden ninguna de las dos m per
go the thing is that what I'm afraid of is that they are
vamos es que lo que yo me temo es que de
going to take it away from me and there will be no
que me lo van a quitar y no va a haber
room to play that is what I fear is that they are
sitio para jugar eso es lo que temo que
going to unban me Because
me lo van a quitar el baneo Porque
being the people that they are I don't see it as
siendo la gente que son no lo veo
impossible but they are going to take it away from me and it won't
imposible pero me lo van a quitar y no
and there will be no room
va a y no va a haber hueco A lo mejor
Maybe I organize it from the shadows the
tipo lo organizo desde las sombras el
squid game I organize from the shadows
squid game lo organizo desde las sombras
and I don't participate in anything I don't show my face or
y no participo en nada no doy la cara ni
anything I only help organize it and that's it
nada solamente ayudo a organizarlo y ya
because with what with the content
está porque con lo que con el contenido
that I'm going to make now I don't want to
que voy a hacer ahora no me quiero
hang out with people like and mind you I'm not doing it
juntar con gente como y ojo no lo hago
for them but for their for the people who
por ellos sino por su por la gente que
see it I don't want to  hang out with
lo vea a ellos no me quiero juntar con
people like Rubius or like guy with Auron
gente como Rubius o como tipo con auron
because they have a community eh that
porque ellos tienen una comunidad eh que
maybe they don't like seeing me with them you
a lo mejor no les gusta verme con ellos
know all for this forging a new me
sabes todo por est forjando un nuevo yo
that Salvadoran is going to go through a lot of
ese salvadoreño va a pasar por muchas
funas that Salvadoran is going to fall that
funas ese salvadoreño va a caer ese
Salvadoran is literally going to fall to the
salvadoreño literalmente va a caer en
lowest in the world Okay but that
los más bajos del mundo Okay pero ese
Salvadoran is going to be reborn like the [ __ ]
salvadoreño va a Renacer como la [__]
goat that Salvadoran is going to be reborn like
cabra ese salvadoreño van a Renacer como
the [ __ ] goat and in 2024 that Salvadoran will
la [__] cabra y en 2024 ese salvadoreño
start the biggest movement of toxicity and
iniciará el movimiento de toxicidad y
racism and of and of the biggest [ __ ] of
racismo y de y de empute más grande de
all of all of all Twitch that
todo de todo de todo Twitch al que le
had to be stopped since Twitch
tuvo que poner freno puesto que Twitch
needed it already of course the bad thing people is
le necesitaba ya clar lo malo gente es
that I can't start with my plan to
que no puedo empezar con mi plan de
take the Twitch Elite because Twitch
tomar el Elite de Twitch porque Twitch
is insisting even though it wants me to do
me está insistiendo aun que quiere que
squ it is telling me places there are no more
haga squ me está diciendo luares ya no
spaces there are 100 reservations waiting for
hay sitio hay 100 reservas esperando que
someone to be removed so knowing the
se quite a alguien para que sabiendo la
people that are on Twitch they get in
peña que hay en Twitch se ponen en
touch and they will prolong the unban and
contacto y van a alargar el desbaneo y
you will remove it until it has
te lo quitaras ya hasta que haya
started  to [ __ ] more How how how
empezado para [__] más Cómo cómo cómo
No but if it's that anyway if it's that it's
No pero si es que de todas maneras si es
not about that anymore it's about the fact that there wo
que ya no se trata de eso se trata de
n't be room or in other words we don't
que no va haber sitio o sea con eso no
count on that but what I believe Is that we do
contemos pero yo lo que creo Es que que
n't count neither Now nor ever or in other words that's
no contemos ni ni Ahora ni nunca o sea
not for me eh the
es que eso no está para mí eh los juegos
squid games are not for me the equit are not
del calamar no están los equit no están
for me it's And since they're insisting
para mí es Y como me están insistiendo
that I do it, well for now I have to or I mean I
que lo haga pues de momento tengo que o
sincerely don't want to do it
sea yo sinceramente no lo quiero hacer
but because I'm fine I don't want to
pero porque estoy bien Yo no quiero
do it but I know that there are a lot of people who are
hacerlo pero sé que ha mucha gente de
excited and it's going to be like I'm going to
ilusión y va a ser como que me voy a
sacrifice myself doing something that I don't want to
sacrificar haciendo algo que no quiero
do as long as it works out that's it but
hacer con tal de que salga ya está pero
I don't want to I don't want to do it you
yo no quiero yo no quiero hacerlo
uploaded the first one but for now I'm
subiste la primera pero de momento estoy
looking for someone who wants to do it instead of
buscando quién lo quiere hacer en vez de
me and who wants to do it to do it
mí y que lo quiera hacer que lo haga
but I can't find anyone capable or rather
pero no encuentro nadie capaz o sea
because people right now don't Or rather someone who
porque la gente ahorita no O sea alguien
wants to organize and move everything
que quiera organizar y moverse todo
nobody wants to you know Don't worry you
nadie quiere sabes No te preocupes que
still gave enough brushstrokes
igualmente diste bastantes pinceladas
Although later we'll go with it returning to
Aunque luego vamos con ello volviendo a
the present comchen has been talking about
la actualidad comchen ha estado hablando
the subject Beto of the event another thing that
del tema Beto del evento otra cosa que
auron also talked about  yesterday It's about the
también habló auron ayer Es sobre la
people in red or about the uninvited people I
gente en rojo o sobre la gente no
also have to come out and
invitada eso también tengo que salir a
talk about that because I think I'm the
hablarlo porque esto creo que yo soy el
most involved because I'm the one
más involucrado porque yo soy el que
announcing the participants and
está anunciando los participantes y esto
Aon said this yesterday
Aon lo dijo ayer
we sent a Twitch list of
hemos mandado una lista Twitch tanto de
participants from both squidcraft 2 and
participantes de squidcraft 2 como del
challenge 3 and many
uno como de desafío 3 y muchas personas
more people that we've seen that have
más que hemos visto que se han
behaved well to include in this series
comportado bien para meter en esta serie
Twitch has put a lot of buts
Twitch nos ha puesto un montón de peros
when it comes to inviting and many have been
a la hora de invitar y a muchos les han
denied entry but not only I don't know
negado la entrada pero no solo no sé a
who they denied entry to in the end eh
quién han negado la entrada al final eh
because I mean they are It's that
porque o sea es que están Es que es que
the list is no longer there I mean I don't know
es que la lista ya no está o sea no sé
who okay [ __ ] Paco what a hair
quiénes vale [__] vaya Paco vaya pelo
I have to go to the hairdresser eh tomorrow
tengo que ir a la peluquería eh mañana
is Sunday I curse my day I have to go to the hairdresser I
es domingo me cago en dí tengo que ir a
don't know who is
la peluquería No sé quiénes están
banned I mean banned these games are
baneados O sea baneado estos juegos son
before the new Netflix series will they make
antes de la nueva serie de Netflix harán
another one when the new games come out 99
otra cuando salgan los nuevos juegos 99
dech Do it No I don't think so we're not going to see
dech Hazlo No no creo no vamos a ver
another year another time they will do Okay but
otro año en otra ocasión harán Vale pero
no I don't think so I don't think so  I don't think so I don't think so there are
no no lo creo no lo creo no lo creo no
gossip channels there are
lo creo hay canales de salseo hay
literally streamers the
literalmente streamers los canales de
gossip channels are not banned okay You have already
salseo no están vetados vale Ya habéis
seen that some
visto que se han anunciado ya algunos
very, very well-known ones have been announced and that
muy pero muy conocidos y que de verdad
we would really like them to be there believe me that I
Nos gustaría que estén créanme que he
have fought until the last second for each one of those on the red list I just hope please that you truly appreciate this effort I mean believe me that I know who you want to see I know who you ask me for the most and I have
quiénes más me piden ustedes y me he
fought for all those people and believe me that
peleado por toda esa gente y créanme que
I have managed to save some but not others
he logrado salvar a unos pero no a otros
and believe me when I tell you you would be
y créanme cuando les digo se
surprised because it is not those
sorprenderían porque no es los que
mentioned in the chat there are people
mencionan en el chat hay gente
literally who literally just
literalmente que literalmente solo
because they do not stream on Twitch but they are not
porque no hacen Stream en Twitch pero
even on Kick Although in
que ni siquiera están en Kick Aunque en
this specific case we are going to talk about
este caso en concreto vamos a hablar de
Steven my people Eh What happens is that they
Steven mi gente Eh Lo que pasa es que me
invited me to the quit ges a guy with the
invitaron a los quit ges un tipo con el
theoretical approval of the
teórico visto bueno de la plataforma
purple platform within those lists Mr
morada dentro de esas listas figuraba Mr
Steven appeared Twitch approved it recommended it and
Steven Twitch lo aprobó lo recomendó y
I went and sent him the invitation
yo fui y le envié la invitación
personally so that
personalmente para que para que él
could play so he could play it's
pudiese jugar para que él pudiese jugar
a shame that in the last few hours
una lástima que las últimas horas se
this clip went viral and I also
haya hecho viral este clip y yo también
arrived Well if we look at it from the
lleg Bueno si lo miramos del lado como
Lore side you are a happy fulfilled person
del Lore tú eres una persona realizada
and those who enter the games are
feliz y los que entran a los juegos son
people without values unfortunate and so on so
gente sin valores desgraciados y así así
on that side it is a sign from life
que por ese lado es una señal de la vida
that you are very lucky grandpa but
de que eres muy afortunada abuelo pero
don't be burned don't be burned I mean do
no seáis ardidos no seáis ardidos O sea
n't be burned because I would have liked this series
no seáis ardido porque esta serie sí me
this one too I turn it
hubiera gustado esta también la enciendo
on foot
a pata y le escupo la cara y contrato
and spit in his face and hire five black guys so that through which you are Blanca palomitas will no longer have to worry if he can broadcast on multiple platforms since he sold his soul to kiik and the problem is that they tell me that I have to broadcast on Twitch
dicen que tengo que transmitir en Twitch
Well I can I can multistream I
Pues que puedo puedo hacer multistream o
mean I can you can multistream dude
sea puedo se puede hacer multistream tío
in the squid game you know we
en el juego del calamar sabes que
would have played up to here on YouTube
hubiéramos jugado hasta aquí en YouTube
dude Twitch and on Kit The problem is knowing
tío Twitch y en Kit El problema es saber
if Kit is causing problems Why Well
si kit pone problemas Por qué Pues
because basically they
porque básicamente le han dado la
kicked him in the ass after we
patadita en el culo después nos hemos
realized after we
dado cuenta después nos hemos dado
realized things eh we have noticed
cuenta de cosas eh nos hemos fijado en
the clip obviously we have seen a clip
el clip obviamente hemos visto un clip
a clip that we believe does not go so much eh
un clip que creemos que no va tanto eh
with the values that Twitch represents and
con los valores que representa Twitch y
with the values that I represent
con los valores que yo represento
as well and that I represent being an [ __ ]
también y que yo represento di ser
both Twitch and I have
cabrón tanto Twitch como yo hemos
decided to leave him out of the competition
decidido dejarlo fuera de la competencia
Eh we have nothing against him we do not
Eh no tenemos nada en contra de él no
know if he is joking if he is if he was you
sabemos si está bromeando si está si
could have had
estaba de podrías haber tenido a
kids and gentleman eria jun we could
chavaleria y señor eria jun podíamos
have broadcast it on the main channel
haberlo emitido en el canal principal
but guys do not be sad do not
pero chicos no os pongáis tristes no
say more what we could or
digáis más lo que podríamos o no
could not have done because it will not be and I do
podríamos haber hecho porque no será e
not know what okay well here you have the
no sé qué okay pues aquí tenéis las
statements of the affected dragonfly
declaraciones de la libelula afectada
they turned that clip and tagged
hicieron virar ese clip y etiquetaron a
Twitch they tagged Comanche to rplay
Twitch etiquetaron a Comanche a rplay a
all the organizers of that event and
todos los organizadores de ese evento y
in short they made me not
en pocas palabras hicieron de que yo no
participate because of that clip eh Comanche
participara por ese clip eh Comanche me
wrote to me and told me that those from T had
escribió y me dijo que los de T habían
seen that clip you say I am not in the mood
visto ese clip pones no estoy de ánimos
that for that reason they could not invite me
que por esa razón no me podían invitar
ready happy I am not going to participate I am not
listo contentos no voy a participar no
going to participate because  they took it out and that's it
voy a participar porque me sacaron y ya
and why did they take me out because they
listo y por qué me sacaron porque
simply made a clip spin
simplemente hicieron virar un clip en
where I simply say something out of
donde Simplemente digo algo fuera de
context and that's all wrong What
contexto y ya eso es todo mal Qué
context could that clip have I mean what
contexo puede tener ese clip O sea qué
context could that clip have I mean not even not
contexo puede tener ese clip o sea ni
even F for the leak
siquiera ni siquiera F por la filtración
but nothing guys let's leave that
pero nada muchachos dejemos eso eso un
aside let's leave that aside I simply
lado dejemos es un lado simplemente les
wanted to tell you eh I also don't want my
quería contar eh tampoco quiero que mi
community to go insulting people to go
comunidad vaya a ir a insultar a ir a a
throw [ __ ] already [ __ ] let's leave that there dude let's leave that there
tirar [__] ya [__] dejemos eso ahí
guys stop
huevón dejemos eso ahí muchachos pare de
telling Twitch and him don't forget both
contar Twitch y él no te olvides tanto
Twitch and I have decided to leave him
Twitch como yo hemos decidido dejarlo
out of the competition you have a lot of
fuera de la competencia tienes tú mucha
capacity for influence with manche
capacidad de incidencia con manche de
really But let's talk about your values
verdad Pero hablemos de tus valores
carlino and with the values that I
carlino y con los valores que yo
represent as well and this is where all
represento también y es aquí donde todo
this really pisses me off because of the
esto me toca las pelotas por la
hypocrisy values that emerged with your
hipocresía valores que emergieron con tu
old self from a few months ago that
antiguo yo de hace poquitos meses ese
Salvadoran would start the thing about the
salvadoreño iniciaría el lo de las
songs they make mento of toxicity
canciones hacen mento de toxicidad
racism and of and of the biggest piss of
racismo y de y de empute más grande de
all of all Twitch we are making
todo de todo de todo Twitch hacemos
the following clip viral right now
viral justo ahora el siguiente clip
also my people or what  I had 200 they said I
también mi gente o qué Tena 200 decían
only have 100 orando I had 300 they said I
tiene 100 no más oando tenía 300 decían
only have 300 and now I have
tiene 300 no más y ahora tengo 500 y
500 and after I'm going to have 600 and I'm going to keep going
después voy a tener 600 y voy a seguir
up and your
subiendo y te va a seguir Ardiendo la
[ __ ] will keep burning and your mother's [ __ ] will burn too
cuca y también le va a arder la cuca la
why Because when she leaves you she
de tu madre por qué Porque a la deja se
sells herself very easily on the streets of your daddy
vende muy fácil en las calles de tu papí
being a [ __ ] worldly man then the very one has been
ser mundista de [__] entonces a la muy
given 80,000
le han pegado 80,000 enfermedades
venereal diseases the very [ __ ] Why Because the
venerias a la muy [__] Por qué Porque la
[ __ ] sells herself very cheap and she already had
[__] se vende bien barato y ya le dio
AIDS syphilis and everything that she had to
sida sífilis y todo lo que le tenía que
give you in your that you come to comment
dar en su que vengas a comentar
stupid things in my [ __ ] chat then
estupideces a mi [__] chat entonces
thank your very [ __ ] of a mother
agradecerle a la muy [__] de tu madre
because she pays for your internet because she
porque te paga el internet porque te da
feeds you and even so she has to put up with
de comer y aún así se tiene que aguantar
such an imbecile child in her house that is
a un niño tan imbécil en su casa que es
so they miss the king of gossip
tan ellos se pierden al rey del salseo
a kiss lauti Thank you very much handsome
un beso lauti Muchísimas gracias guapo
such an imbecile that he knows absolutely
tan imbécil que no conoce absolutamente
nothing or rather because of the filth of the  your mother you have to
nada o sea por la roña de la tu madre
be such a son of a [ __ ] and you can
tenes que ser tan hijo de la y podes
come comment 500 in the [ __ ] chat
venir a comentar 500 en el [__] chat
Okay then thank
Okay entonces agradecele a la roña de la
your filthy [ __ ] thank her these are
cuca de tu madre agradecele estos son
the values that get hard I
los valores que a se la ponen dura
suppose and with the values that I
Supongo y con los valores que yo
represent you also remember the
represento también os acordáis de la de
classism Come on We apply it just in
clasismo Venga va Lo aplicamos por si
case speak like You have to speak says
acaso habla como Tienes que hablar dice
Ares correct I am speaking like I have to speak
Ares correcto estoy hablando como tengo
and how I have to speak is
que hablar y como tengo que hablar es
how I decide to speak not like you are going to
como yo decido hablar no como tú me vas
tell me to speak [ __ ] or like my
a decir que yo hable cabrón ni como mi
country gave me how to speak I am going to speak
país me di como habl yo voy a hablar
how I decide to speak to myself why Because
como yo decido hablarme por qué Porque
I speak however I feel like
yo hablo como se me da la perra gana
something that you can't do why
algo que tú no puedes hacer por qué
Because you are a poor son of a [ __ ] you
Porque tú eres un pobre hijo de laa tú
are [ __ ] I mean you are
eres una [__] O sea tú estás
writing this and you are a poor piece of
escribiendo esto y eres un pobre de
[ __ ] okay So you have to
[__] okay Entonces tú tienes que
literally rule and speak like a
literalmente regir y hablar como una
normal person not me I can speak
persona la normal yo no Yo puedo hablar
like me like me like I want I can
como yo como yo como yo quiera yo puedo
as a Mexican as a Salvadoran
como mexicano como salvadoreño
Puerto Rican Argentine I don't care
puertorriqueño argentino me da igual por
why because I have enough money
qué porque tengo el suficiente dinero
to do any accent and I  pela
para hacer cualquier acento y me la pela
Instead you don't you go to work and you
En cambio tú no tú vas al trabajo y
have to say hello boss how are you
tienes que decir hola jefe Cómo estás
good morning you have to say to your
Buenos días tú tienes que decirle a tu
boss good morning [ __ ] that's what
jefe Buenos días cabrón eso es lo que
happens that's the difference between you and me
pasa es la diferencia entre tú y yo
[ __ ] That's the difference between you and
cabrón Esa es la diferencia entre tú y
me you go to your [ __ ] job you
yo que tú vas a tu fucking trabajo tú
go to your [ __ ] job and and he says
vas a tu fucking trabajo y y le dice
hello boss how are you bossy good morning
hola jefe qué tal jefecito Buenos días
then you have to speak
entonces tú tienes que hablar
politely every day not me [ __ ] Thank you very
educadamente todos los días yo no cabrón
much lauti Thank you very
Muchas gracias lauti Muchísimas gracias
much Thank you very much man watch but here
Muchísimas gracias tío ojo pero aquí
everyone today who has
todo el mundo hoy que ha regalado
given away members has given away 50 members I'm still seeing on screen three people who have given away 50 members What's wrong with you Saturday night fever Saturday night fever very crazy Let's see how many members we have so far
cuántos miembros llevamos en lo que va
tonight 125 well 125 it can't be
de noche 125 bueno 125 no pueden ser
clear that's because not
claro eso es porque no se han sumado
all the new ones have joined Hey guys I think it would be
todos los nuevos Oye chavales yo creo
nice if we reached
que sería bonito que llegáramos a los
3000 eh I mean there's nothing left Now when they
3000 eh o sea queda nada Ahora cuando se
finish adding up we'll see how much there is but
terminen de sumar vemos cuánto hay pero
come on if there are at least 150 we're
vamos si como mínimo hay 150 estamos
talking about  we're at
hablando de que estamos en
2900 and something eh I mean there's nothing left nothing
2900 y pico eh o sea falta nada nada
nothing for 3000 eh I don't I don't I
nada para los 3000 eh yo noed yo no yo
can do it however I want Why
puedo haar como se me de la gana Por qué
Because I'm rich because I'm a millionaire you're
Porque soy rico porque soy millonario tú
not a [ __ ] You're not you're a piece of
no lo eres cabrón Tú no eres tú eres un
[ __ ] okay Okay Those are the ranges
[__] okay Okay Esos son los rangos
between you and me [ __ ]
entre tú y yo cabrón valores
exemplary values and with the values that I
ejemplarizantes y con los valores que yo
also represent that I apply with a
represento también que aplicó con unos
few there's no lack of detail [ __ ]
cuantos no le falta detallle [__]
[ __ ] with four viewers Come on [ __ ]
mierdita con cuatro viewers Órale
don't leave your house today son of
[__] no salgas de tu casa hoy hijo de
a [ __ ] we've got you under control you [ __ ] [ __ ]
tu madre ya te tenemos controlado cabrón
eh [ __ ] [ __ ] let's see let's see
a la [__] eh A la [__] put a ver a ver
at least show your face you ugly piece of
a ver mínimo da la cara el [__] feo de
[ __ ] let's see Don't [ __ ] with me four
[__] a ver No [__] cabrón de cuatro
smart ones pass 60 gey we're going to give the
vivos pas 60 gey le vamos a dar el
Partner chat chat I feel happy today
Partner chat chat Me siento feliz hoy
today I'm going to give the Partner to a
hoy le voy a dar el Partner a un
stranger on Twitch to a piece of [ __ ] on
desconocido de Twitch a un mierdita de
Twitch today I feel happy I already did let's
Twitch hoy me siento feliz Ya ya hice a
see today I already went Good today I already went Good today I already
ver hoy ya fui Bueno hoy ya fui Bueno
went good chat today my my d of the
hoy ya fui bueno chat hoy mi mi d del
day I already did my d of the day I already did it
día Ya lo hice mi d del día Ya lo hice
people I already went Well I already gave the
ya gente ya fui Bueno ya le Ya le di el
Partner to a little twitchy brat I'm going
Partner a un mocosito de twitchy le voy
to bring food to the table of a
a llevar comida a la mesa de un
Colombian how good I feel Today I'm going to go to
colombiano que bien me siento Hoy me voy
sleep happy because I gave the
a ir a dormir feliz porque le di el
Partner to a stupid Colombian like
Partner a un colombianito [__] como
you So I'm going to I don't care car a I don't give a
tú Entonces le voy no me importa car a
[ __ ] I don't give a
me importa un culo a mí me importa un
[ __ ] having 10 viers five viers four
culo tener 10 viers cinco viers cuatro
viers I don't give a [ __ ] the truth is I do
viers me importa un culo la verdad a mí
n't care about any of this But then
no me importa nada de esto Pero entonces
why are you doing it If you don't
por qué lo estás haciendo Si no te
care because you're very lazy why
importa por es que es muy huevón por qué
talk to me why do you give me light
habla conmigo para qué me da luz a mí
also voted by everyone who was
también votada por todos los que estaban
on the list no the 200 spots were already
en la lista no los 200 cupos ya estaban
occupied and now that they remove the veto they are
ocupados y ahora que les quitan el veto
going to be left out Likewise this
se van a quedar fuera Igualmente esta
move by Twitch is to later say
jugada de Twitch es para luego decir e
that I White the veto of the tw Well they have
que yo les White el veto de los tw Bueno
n't finished announcing yet there are
todavía no se han terminado de anunciar
50 left to announce eh there are 50 left to
faltan 50 por anunciar eh faltan 50 por
announce LoL Tas has been commenting
anunciar LoL Tas ha estado comentando
on this too let's see if  it's here here
sobre esto también a ver si es aquí aquí
responding to a to a tweet of mine of those
respondiendo a un a un tet mío de estos
that t was Comanche says that many
de la que t era Comanche dice que muchos
asked him to remove Mr Steven from the
le pidieron sacar a Mr Steven de los
skid but they left him alone tanking the
skid pero lo dejaron solo tanqueando la
funa they refused to be refused to
funa rechazaron estar rechazaron
participate and I Juan arit plex and oo and
participar y yo Juan arit plex y oo y el
Dallas says Hey Comanche I'm participating
Dallas dice Oye Comanche yo participo
but only if you sing me one of
pero solo si me cantas una canción de
your songs while I twerk if not no
las tuyas mientras hago twerk si no no
[ __ ] I hadn't realized it's true no no I hadn't
[__] no me había dado cuenta es verdad
realized it's a it's a
no no no me había dado cuenta es un es
host it's not a saasa I mean I
un es una [__] no es un saasa O sea me
thought it was like Eh I thought it was like
creía que era como Eh me creía que era
a joke or something but no no he
como como una broma o algo pero no no le
's hitting him like you're getting
está pegando una [__] como te estás
here like very well put with that
poniendo aquí como muy bien puesto con
cli and then over here he posted
el cli ese y luego por aquí ha puesto
this you participate in the
esto tú participo en la serie de
Comanche series by skidka the most family
Comanche de skidka el creador más family
friendly creator in Spanish who
friendly de habla hispana el cual me ha
hired me to be a twerk while he
contratado para ser twerk mientras él
sings things about How I Move My Cucumber
canta cosas sobre Cómo mueve mi pepino
while I twerk on a platform
mientras hago twerk en una plataforma
as fair with its creators as
tan justa con sus creadores como es
Twitch and they give it a note of  the
Twitch y le ponen una nota de la
community dude those of the
comunidad tío los de la notas de la
community notes dude mm are tremendously
comunidad tío mm son tremendamente
stupid eh I mean they think they think
[__] eh o sea se cree se cree que
they have an important profession there a
tienen ahí una una profesión importante
position in I mean a a a
un cargo en o sea una una una
responsibility you know no no this is
responsabilidad sabes no no esto es tío
tremendously stupid dude luare tells me
tremendamente [__] me dice luare
in the click that you put on Twitter he took out
en el click que pusiste en Twitter sacó
the Mental Health letter to
la carta de la Salud Mental para
justify that stage I'm here for
justificar esa etapa Yo estoy aquí por
two reasons but but yeah I mean he was
dos razones pero pero sí O sea él estaba
there that focus focus I remember
ahí de que centrate centrate me acuerdo
that I also had a call with Twitch
que tuve una llamada también con Twitch
and he said Hey we've seen your
y me dijo Oye hemos visto tu
behavior we don't like what's
comportamiento no nos gusta qué está
going on Everything's fine and they told me and of course it
pasando Todo bien y me dijeron y claro
was like the medications had
era como que los medicamentos me habían
altered my entire my personality and the whole thing
alterado todo mi mi personalidad y todo
and they told me if you behave
el pedo y me dijeron si te comportas
better we promise to do an event with you
mejor prometemos hacer un evento contigo
on behalf of the tamam eh that they are not a
por parte de la tamam eh que no sean un
Rivals and sponsor an event but we
Rivals y patrocinar un evento pero
need you to behave better I mean
ocupamos que te comportes mejor o sea
Twitch was very nice in that aspect
Twitch fue muy lindo en ese aspecto
you know everyone everyone was
sabes todo el mundo todo el mundo estaba
worried about me I didn't know what was happening And
preocupado por mí no sabía qué pasaba Y
Twitch told me Twitch lat spoke to me and
Twitch me dijo Twitch lat me habló y me
said Hey we need you to behave
dijo Oye necesitamos que te comportes
better and after  the squids are doing
mejor y te después de los squid hacemos
an event with you and I tell you auron has
un evento contigo y te digo auron ha
been someone who was there very very
sido sido alguien que estaba ahí muy muy
attentive to me and I thank him. I mean I
pendiente de mí y le agradezco a él o
think that if this goes well it will
sea yo creo que si esto sale bien va a
obviously be thanks to Rubius too
ser obviamente gracias a Rubius también
because Rubius despite being
porque Rubius a pesar de estar
disappointed with the project and the buts
desilusionado del proyecto de los peros
that Twitch Rivals and Twitch USA have put up
que ha puesto Twitch Rivals y Twitch
is still there supporting me. I mean, you
Estados Unidos sigue ahí bancando o sea
know, my [ __ ] respect for auron. The truth is that
sabes mi [__] respeto a auron la verdad
from here I have my [ __ ] respect for auron
desde aquí mi [__] respeto a auron
because that guy was with me through thick and
porque porque ese cabrón estaba conmigo
thin, all the
en las buenas y en las malas todas las
people who say that ao is not a good friend
personas que dicen que ao no es bu amigo
who doesn't care about his friends
que no se preocupa por sus amigos me
can suck my left ball and my
pueden comer el huevo izquierdo el
right ball and in the process shave my dick and
derecho y de paso pelarme la [__] y
start sucking on me honestly. Oh, the
empezá mea a chupar sinceramente Ay el
guy just said that the
tío acaba de acaba de decir que el tema
vocabulary issue was because he's
del vocabulario era por porque está mal
mentally unhealthy and immediately as it
de salud mental y seguido tal y como
ends he sends everyone back to
termina le vuelve a mandar a todos a
suck his penis and jerk him off. Hello and
chuparle el pene y hacerle paja Hola y
you.
tú
[Music]
[Música]